One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Fearsome Ability of the Shadow Fruit!
The Ultimate Number 900!
It's not over!
Despite cutting him, he's still a zombie.
He'll keep getting up!
You...!
Wait a sec... I've seen you before...
Worry not.
I've finished him off already.
Finished?
These zombies have a weak point.
What is that?!
That's the zombie's soul.
Soul?
It's coming out right before our eyes!
Now, return to your master!
Commander Tararan!
The commander was defeated!
He completely stopped moving.
What did you do?!
Purification.
Look!
There's no doubt, he is the "Humming One".
He's the man who caused a ruckus in Thriller Bark five years ago.
Inform master!
This spider's web is indeed strong against physical force, but still weak to fire.
You're right!
It melted!
Straw Hat and the others were abducted.
It seems you know quite a lot about this island.
Yes.
However, I'm not quite sure how to put this.
The fact that they've been captured means there is a strong possibility it may already be too late.
What?!
Too late?!
P-Please don't get mad at me.
Let's keep a straight face!
Even though as a skeleton, I don't have a face!
Skull joke!
Stop it, he's already dead.
Anyway,
Stop joking and listen to me.
Stop it, he's already dead.
It is as I told you on the ship, when my ship's rudder failed,
I began wandering the sea alone decades ago...
I thought of escaping this evil sea, but with the rudder broken I was just a puppet of the sea current.
That was more than five years ago.
And just like you now, I eventually was lead to Thriller Bark.
I wanted to leave the Florian Triangle no matter what.
Hoping that there might be parts to fix the rudder on the island, I investigated.
When I entered, I found nothing but zombies and monsters in the way.
Before long I was captured and brought to this building.
Inside I saw a combat dancer who was caught earlier and a patched corpse which they called a marionette.
Afterwards, a terrifying and huge man appeared, and...!
He tore the man's shadow from the floor!
He cut it off!
His shadow was cut off?
I thought my eyes were deceiving me... even though...
I don't have any eyes.
Stop joking or I'll kick your ass!
I don't mind if you do.
I was to have the same fate before long.
The one whose shadow was taken collapsed where he stood.
On the other hand, his severed shadow was pressed inside the unmoving body of the marionette.
I didn't think that was possible...
How he did it, I'm unsure...
But, the marionette corpse just...
Started moving on its own!
What do you mean?
A shadow is another soul that goes and moves along with you anywhere.
It follows you from birth to death.
It's a soul that will never leave you, that will always obey and follow you.
The man that seizes these, and has them obey his will is...
The Royal Warlord of the Sea, Gekko Moriah!
The user of the Shadow Fruit.
A devil fruit, huh?
As long as there's a corpse, he can use a shadow to bring forth a zombie.
The problem is that the genius surgeon who creates these tough creatures, Doctor Hogback... has friends.
In some cases, he gets parts from different graveyards...
Using the corpses of legendary warriors to revive them.
Moreover, he has an immense amount of enumerated marionettes still stored in a freezer in his lab.
Dr. Hogback...
So that famous doctor came to this place after the incident of his disappearance to help a pirate.
Then, the zombies' bodies can move, so it's not like they've been resurrected.
Correct.
The shadow holds both the personality and fighting skills of its owner.
The physical strength of the marionette is limited by the power of it's body.
When both strong shadow and body are merged, the result is an even more powerful zombie.
That is why Moriah so eagerly desires the shadows of bounty heads.
I see.
They were after us from the start.
So that's the whole story of Thriller Bark.
To Moriah, the zombie's most important characteristic might be obedience.
The stronger the warrior the harder it must be to make it listen.
True... they receive the same fighting spirit and skill as their owner.
The strong ones are set adrift at sea after they lose consciousness.
Then, they...!
This is bad.
They're safe yet.
We have time.
Right now I will tell you the best plan we have.
So please, trust me and do as I say.
Trust you?!
Skull Shock!
I haven't had a conversation like this in decades! It's so fun!
We're listening, so tell us quickly.
Okay...
Master!
The Three Mysterious Persons have arrived!
That was quick. Enter.
Please, come inside.
You finally came.
Make me the Pirate King.
Very soon.
You're no Pirate King!
The Pirate King will be...
Me!
Hey! Untie this string you giant leek!
Usopp, Nami, Chopper, Sanji, Zoro... Give them all back!
Where did you take them, leek?!
What a splendidly strong man.
So this is Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
You mentioned many names.
We've only captured three of you so far.
The Pirate Hunter Zoro and a blond guy with no wanted poster.
Could that blond guy be Sanji...?
What?!
Hey, it seems Zoro and Sanji also got caught.
No way, and Luffy was also caught!
H-How come that monstrous trio got caught so easily?!
I don't know who these guys are, but they're definitely bad news!
By the way, what happened with those three, Perona?
The Risky Brothers were supposed to deliver them...
They didn't bring them to Kumashi.
Didn't they escape while they were being delivered?
They're talking about us.
Don't say it. You... Don't say it!
I told you not to open your mouth!
You're too strict with Kumashi...
Way too strict.
Anyways, I was trying to get a hold of my bride when those three...
Ran into your garden and caused a disturbance.
Hey, wait a second.
That means... Hogback...!
Bastard, do you mean that one of you laid a hand on my bride?!
So that's what happened before!
Your bride is not coming.
What was that, Cindry!?
Hey! Hey! Cindry-chan, you're making it worse!
And why did you step out in front of me?
Yours won't be coming either.
What a low blow! Where did that come from?!
Stop! Stop!
Stop this pointless discussion.
If some pirates got away, then you guys can do something about it later.
I gathered you here to celebrate the creation of a great fighting asset.
Who is that guy!?
Master, that pirate bit the cage apart to escape!
He...!
Bit the cage!
What're you gonna do to catch me now?!
What a promising man!
Wait, Absalom, we're inside a room.
I'll stop him.
Like you'd catch me, idiot!
Negative Hollow!
If I were to be reborn, I want to become a sea slug...
The man who just said he wanted to be Pirate King now wants to be a sea slug...
Atrocious...
Turn the light on!
What're you doing, damn it!
You'll regret this!
W-What's that?!
My shadow...!
I finally have it!
The 300 million fighting power!
With this, the Ultimate Special Zombie can be created!
Go back to the ship?
To the Sunny?
Correct.
The worst case scenario is that your friends have been captured and their shadows have been stolen.
However, having their shadow stolen isn't going to kill them.
Take a look at what happened to me!
Ah, I died!
That's a different story!
Anyway...
In short, even if they got their shadow stolen, they won't die.
That's right.
However, the moment their shadows are taken, they become vulnerable as they lose consciousness.
And won't wake up for two days.
During this time they put those who are strong into boats and cast them off from Thriller Bark.
I've said this before but, do you know why they do that?
So that the victims won't attempt to return to the island and reclaim their shadows, right?
Precisely.
Then, why not just kill them while they're unconscious?
They cannot.
This is very important, so listen carefully.
First of all...
Although the body and the shadow may be separated, they're part of one being.
If the body dies, then the shadow is doomed as well.
In other words, the moment that happens, the zombie will also perish.
This means trouble for the enemy, so they make sure to keep the body alive.
Which means that, even if your friends have been stripped off their shadows...
They are surely alive and are being taken back to the ship.
That's why...!
If you two become victims as well, this will turn into the worst case scenario!
Everyone would've lost their shadows and will be left to wander the sea.
But something can still be done. If we wake up your friends...
We'll have one chance to figure out how to recover the stolen shadows.
Did you get all that?
I see.
That makes sense.
Take this, you two.
What is it?
The zombies' weakness.
It's effectiveness against the Spider Monkey is proof!
Weakness?
What is this?
Salt.
Salt?
So it's kinda like we're defeating some evil being by purifying it?
Well, you could say that.
The zombies are originally animated by the power of the devil fruit.
Just as the sea nullifies the abilities of a devil fruit user...
the salt which has the sea's power undoes the bond between the false soul and the corpse.
I see.
So that thing that flew out of the monkey's mouth a little while ago was the shadow from within his body.
To think they had such a weakness...
Now then, to defeat the Zombies, simply throw the salt into their mouths!
That's the trick!
The only trick!
The trick!
The trick, the trick, the trick!
But Brook...
Why is it that you happen to know so much about this island and the zombies?
When my shadow was stolen five years ago...
Naturally, I was cast off in my ship, but luckily enough I woke up in time to find a way back.
And then I returned to the island...
To fight...
The zombie that has my shadow!
But... I was completely defeated.
I shamefully ran to save my life...
No matter what...
No matter what... I didn't want to die.
Because I was the sole survivor from my ship.
Because I promised my friends that one day I'd escape from this Devil Sea...
I shamefully ran to save my life!
And though I managed to live a long while, I was unable to achieve any resolution.
That's why... I will not escape this time!
Until I beat that man and recover my shadow I-
Well then...
Please excuse me, I'll go ahead.
Have a good day.
Wait a minute!
While we're still at it, just answer me one more question.
L-Luffy!
What was that... just now?
His shadow...!
His shadow was ripped off!
It's just like the story that skeleton Brook told us.
If his shadow was taken... then that means this guy also took Brook's!
I can't believe it...
How come he can do such a thing?
Kumashi! You were blabbering again weren't you?!
You're too strict with Kumashi...
Way too strict.
This guy will bring me one step closer to being the Pirate King, right Hogback?
Since the day I met you ten years ago, I've served you for the day Number 900 would be made.
With that shadow we can create the greatest zombie ever made...
And without a doubt, it'll become a huge source of power for us!
The day that I will be known worldwide as the Graveyard King has come closer!
My dream kingdom where all the world's cute things will become zombies and serve me is before my eyes!
Even the most insolent bastard will become an obedient zombie if I take his shadow!
I'll turn this world into one full of obedient zombies!
If I had a servant like this back then...
I wouldn't have lost to that idiot Kaidou in the New World!
Let's wake him up already!
Gyoro!
Nin!
Bao!
Yes, master!
Open the door to the special freezer!
Right away, master!
Just you wait, 900.
Spider Mouse.
Dump Straw Hat Luffy's body on his ship.
And don't forget to remove the thread, it'll be troublesome if he dies.
Yes!
Please wait! I have a report!
What is it?
Just now, Commander Spider Monkey Tararan was defeated!
Defeated?
That's not possible, unless his shadow is extracted.
His shadow was extracted!
Absalom...
The only man capable of such a thing, is him!
The Chivalrous Humming Swordsman!
It seems the report Hildon gave me wasn't wrong.
This is terrible!
The Humming One has been freeing lots of shadows!
Before I knew it, there were countless victims!
At this rate, the nightmare from five years ago will be repeated!
Damn... He's the only man who could tell the zombies' weakn-
Huh?
How did he find out-
Cindry-chan, why're you standing in front of me?!
I've heard about him but... what is he like?
Perona, you don't know what he looks like?
Then, that's why he wasn't spotted.
Master!
That troublemaker has come once again...
Like I care about such a thing, idiot!
You take care of it!
H-Hold on!
Now, on to the freezer.
Still, the current situation is...
Idiot! Say that in the first place!
In that case, we should be able to contain him.
Yes.
If there's a problem when he wakes up, report it.
Now go ahead and throw Straw Hat out already.
Yes!
Heave-ho!
Idiot, don't go out!
It seems being stripped of your shadow won't kill you!
It didn't kill Brook.
We can't go out yet.
We'll wait for our chance!
It seems like they're going to do something with Luffy's shadow.
We need to see what happens to it so we can get it back later!
Those two are no longer here.
Where did they go?
I can't believe they got Tararan.
Where's the enemy?!
I'll cut them in an instant!
Franky.
What do you want?! I'm not crying!
Idiot, don't look this way!
Why did you ask him... such a question?
Shut up! Don't mind me!
Dammit! I love that skeleton now!
There isn't a guy that good anywhere!
Damn!
You're right.
As I thought, you're not gonna give up by merely kicking you out.
Of course!
Don't you know my name?
Anyone who hears the name Swordmaster Ryuuma will cower in fear.
Silence!
You're my shadow!
There's a big difference between our bodies.
You shall return...
To my feet!
I can't wait!
Back when I saw his corpse in the Ice Country, I couldn't help but tremble.
It takes my breath away to think this repulsive thing rampaged through the seas 500 years ago!
He took the entire island of each country he conquered to expand his own territory...
Cold...!
And thus he built the so called Evil Country.
The very founder of the Country-Puller legend is right there!
This will be the best zombie ever create-!
The legend will be reborn once again!
Now... it's time to resurrect...!
The only man in history...!
The wild warrior that was called the Demon!
Oars!
Translation & initial syncing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality checking, Sewil
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee